So, tell us! How are things
with you and Lelouch?
ねえねえルルーシュくんとはどうなってるの？
You're the official school
authorized couple, aren't you?
学校公認のカップルだもんね
Have you kissed already?!
もうキスはした？
Th-That was just for the event.
We haven't done anything...
あれはただのイベントで まだなんにも
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Everyone knows you have a thing for Lelouch.
照れることはないさ
おまえがルルーシュに惚れてるのはみんな知ってる
Oh, Coach Villetta, not you, too!
もう！ヴィレッタ先生まで
But you do love him.
Enough to shoot me, right?
好きなんだろう？私を撃つくらいに
えっ？
つらかったよ　自分を撃った女と 毎日にこやかにくらさなくてはないなんて
It's been hard, you know?
Having to spend each day
smiling at the girl who shot me.
But I've had to wear
the mask of a teacher.
だが私は 教師という仮面をかぶらなければならなかった
Shirley Fenette...
How dare you have shot me!
シャーリー フェネットよくも私を撃ってくれたな
ルル！
Lulu!
That's right... While Lulu was
Zero, he killed my father.
そう ルルはゼロで お父さんのかたきなんだ
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
ASSASSIN FROM THE PAST
So, Jianmenguan has fallen?
剣門関はおちたか
マカオの空軍施設もおさえた
We've also taken over
the air base in Macau.
カザフスタンの守りには朝比奈とホングをまわせばいいとして
We should send Asahina and
Hong Gu to defend Kazakhstan,
健業の内政担当は水無瀬と杉山にまかせるか
so why don't we send Minase and Sugiyama
to take charge of municipal affairs in Kengyo?
順調みたいだね 兄さん
Looks like things are going smoothly, big brother.
Our so-called enemies are just local
military factions who don't want to join us,
敵といっても 我々を受け入れない地方軍閥が
but only use their forces without
coordinating with each other.
バラバラに兵をあげているだけだからな
地方軍閥をまとめられる旗印は 兄さんが先に手にいれてしまったし
Besides, you already got the one
banner they'd all fight under, big brother.
そういうことだ
Exactly.
どこに？
Where to?
I'm going to check out things in Ikebukuro.
イケブクロの様子をみてくる
宿題の続きは 帰ってからみてやるよ
I'll have a look at the rest of the
homework when I get back.
See you later.
いってらっしゃい
う～にゃ
Lulu was Zero. And Coach Villetta was a soldier.
ルルはゼロだった
ヴィレッタ先生は軍人
カレンは黒の騎士団
Kallen was one of the Black Knights.
じゃあニーナは？会長は？リヴァルは？
Then what about Nina?
And the Prez? And Rivalz?
おかしいのは 学校だけ？
Is the school the only
place that's so weird?
どうしてナナちゃんが総督なの？
Why is Nunna now the viceroy?
何がうそで 何が本当なの？
What are the lies and what is the truth?
準急列車は3番線に10分遅れて停車します
The local express will arriving on platform
three ten minutes behind schedule.
The local train leaving on track
two will arrive at Ohkubo first.
オオクボ駅までは2番線より発車します各駅停車が先着します
いいだろう初期段階としては充分だ
Very well. This is fine for the initial stage.
All right, then we'll keep up
the work using this style.
ではこのスタイルで作業を続行します
お客さまにキャンペーンのお知らせです
現在期間限定
シャーリー！
Shirley!
待って！僕だよ
Wait! It's me.
あっ
どうしたの？急によびだして
What's wrong?
Why'd you suddenly call me out here?
う うん
シャーリー？
Shirley!
Lelouch.
ルルーシュ
ルルーシュは？デートか？
Where's Lelouch? On a date?
He went to test out the G trains.
Ｇ列車のテストにいきましたよ
Heh. My, how convenient.
ふんなら 好都合だ
え？
ロロ おまえはなぜ寝返った？
Rolo, why did you betray our side?
私と違い嚮団から派遣されている以上
Unlike me, you were dispatched
here by the Order, so...
Why are you asking me that?
What's between my brother and me is...
なんですか？その質問は
兄さんと僕の間を
B7 to control.
Suspicious person sighted near the chapel.
Ｂ７より司令部へに
礼拝堂付近に不審者発見
Ｂ５　Ｂ９が確保に向かいました
B5 and B9 have
moved in to apprehend him.
ふんルルーシュの居場所をきいただけでこれか
Look what happened just by
asking where Lelouch is.
ジェレミア卿！なぜ
Lord Jeremiah! But how?!
対象はクラブハウスに向かっています
Target is moving towards the clubhouse.
B2 and B8 have been eliminated as well.
Ｂ２　Ｂ８も排除されました
校内放送を
Make a school wide announcement!
Get the students out of the target's vicinity!
他の生徒を対象エリア外に
This is an emergency announcement
to all students from the academy.
学園より生徒の皆さんに緊急連絡です
Please stay away
from the clubhouse area.
クラブハウス近くに立ち入らないでください
A suspicious person has
been sighted there. I repeat...
不審者が目撃されています
繰り返します
Out of my way. I have no desire
to kill a woman if I don't have to.
どきたまえ
なるべくなら女性は殺したくない
私もなるべくなら無駄な殺生は避けたかったのですが
I also would like to avoid
any unnecessary killing.
ほう
Oh?
En garde!
いざ
Mechanical?!
機械？
Thanks to Zero.
ゼロのおかげでな
彼らは神を殺すと
They say they're going to kill God.
God, you say?
神だと？
I thought they were speaking
metaphorically, but now...
何かの比喩表現かとも思いましたが
少なくとも 彼等はそう信じています
At the very least,
they believe it!
Ridiculous.
There's no such thing as God!
バカな神など存在するわけがない
That's right.
そうだね
背中に翼のはえた女神様とか
No winged goddesses or long-bearded
old men. Not that sort of God...
長いひげの老人とか そんな神様はね
コーネリア様
Princess Cornelia!
どんなギアスを使うかわからぬ
We don't know what sort
of Geass he possesses!
相手が子どもといえど油断はできない
You can't let your guard down,
even for a child.
Yes, that's right.
そうだね
さすがは音にきこえたコーネリア皇女殿下
You live up to your reputation,
Princess Cornelia.
ぼくも伯父として誇りに思うよ
As your uncle,
I'm proud of you.
バカな
Impossible!
僕らは誓ったんだ
We made a vow. If there was a god
who made men fight each other...
人々を争わせるような神なら
殺してしまおうって
then we would kill him.
Even if you are a cyborg,
I can still hit your exposed living parts!
たとえ改造人間でも むきだしの生体部分なら！
You have good aim!
狙いはよし
とめます！ルルーシュ様のために！
I'll stop you!
For Master Lelouch's sake!
よき体術が
Your martial arts are impressive.
But not good enough
to beat Jeremiah Gottwald!
されどこのジェレミア ゴットバルトには
咲世子！
Sayoko!
Steal time!
時を奪う！
Sayoko!
Get him while I hold him still!
咲世子僕がこいつを止めている間に
わかりました
Gotcha!
そんな 僕のギアスが
Impossible! My Geass!
It should stop time for anyone, but!
絶対停止の結界を
ロロ ランペルージ
So, Rolo Lamperouge!
I thought you'd been hooked in, too!
やはり籠絡されていたか
How could you break my Geass?
どうして ギアスが
それゆえに私が選ばれた
Because I was chosen!
To be an assassin for the Order!
嚮団からの刺客として
やっぱり兄さんを殺しに
So, you have come to kill big brother!
ジェレミア卿！
Lord Jeremiah!
ヴィレッタ
Villetta!
Lelouch has snared you, as well?!
おまえもルルーシュにとりこまれたのか？
Lelouch is in the Ikebukuro
station building right now!
ルルーシュは今イケブクロの駅ビルにいます
お願いです ジェレミア卿
Lord Jeremiah,
I beg of you! Let me go!
私を解放してください
ひきうけた
Agreed.
どうしようスザク君を呼び出してみたけど
What do I do? I called Suzaku out here,
but what do I say to him?
何をいえば
ルルもいるし
With Lulu here, too.
シャーリーどういうつもりだ？
Shirley, what are you playing at?
Or was it Suzaku
who called her out here?
いや　誘ったのはスザクのほうか？
リヴァルは ルルーシュがずっと日本にいたと言っていた
Rivalz told me that Lelouch has
been here in Japan the entire time.
Intelligence from the O.S.I.
backs that up as well, but...
機情の報告も白だと証言しているのにも
なぜ僕は信じられないんだ
But why don't I believe it?
ヴィレッタ あなたは兄さんを裏切るんですか
Villetta, are you betraying
big brother? Or...
それとも
ルルーシュに連絡しろ
Contact Lelouch.
ここは私が守るから
I have to protect this place,
so the rest of you go to Ikebukuro.
おまえたちはイケブクロに向かえ
ルルーシュが待ち受ければ
If Lelouch is ready for him,
we may be able to pin Lord Jeremiah on two sides.
ジェレミア卿をはさみうちにできる
言わなくちゃ スザクくんに
I have to tell Suzaku!
ルルはゼロなの お父さんのかたきで
That Lulu is Zero
and that he killed my father!
境界線だな ここは
This is the boundary line, isn't it?
租界とゲットー
Between the settlement
and the ghettos.
でもなくしてみせるいつか
But we have to try and erase it.
Some day.
待ってこの２人が共犯だったら
Hold it.
What if these two are accomplices?
エリア１１を日本に戻すために
To turn Area 11 back into Japan?
そうよ ２人は昔からの親友で
That's it! They've been best
friends since a long way back!
どうしたんだ シャーリー
Shirley, what's wrong?
はっ！いやー！
No!
Stay away from me!
来ないで！
シャーリー！
Shirley!
Liars! You're all a bunch of fakes!
うそつき！みんな偽物のくせに！
私は
I won't!
No! Let me go! Let me go!
いや！離して！離して！
だめだ！離さない！
No! I won't let you go!
I don't want to lose you.
I don't want to lose anyone else!
俺はもう 俺はもう 失いたくないんだ
何一つも失いたくない
Not one more person...
シャーリー
Shirley!
うん
Suzaku!
スザク！
ねえ まえにもこんなことあったよね
You did that before, didn't you?
え
ほら ふたりがアーサーをつかまえようとして
You know, like you did
while trying to catch Arthur.
ああ そういえば
Now that you mention it...
たしかにあったなそんなことが
You're right, we did do this before.
引き上げる役はいつもスザクくんだね
Suzaku is always the one
who pulls you back up.
ルルーシュが上だったら ふたりとも落ちてるよ
If Lelouch was on top,
we both would have fallen.
Listen to the exercise nut here!
体力バカが
そこまで言うんだったら 落ちる前に助けろ
If you're gonna brag,
why didn't you save me before I fell?
無理言うなよ
Don't be ridiculous!
何笑ってる ルルーシュはユフィを
What am I laughing for?
After what Lelouch did to Euphy!
違う一人なんだ ルルは
I was wrong.
He's alone. Lulu is...
ああ ごめん
Oh. Sorry.
兄さん 気をつけてそっちにジェレミアが向かってる
Big brother, be careful!
Jeremiah's on his way to you!
嚮団の刺客なんだ僕のギアスがきかなかった
He's an Order assassin.
My Geass didn't work on him!
あいつが生きていた？刺客とはどういうことだ？
He's alive?
What do you mean by assassin?
わからないとにかく 僕らがいくまで 無茶はしないで
I'm not sure. Anyway, don't do
anything rash until we get there!
何かあったのかい？
Is something up?
This is bad. With Suzaku here...
まずいなスザクがいては
友達からの電話ってわけじゃなさそうだけど
You don't look like that
phone call was from a friend.
Ow!
ダメだよ～ スザクくん
Suzaku, stop that!
Doesn't my problem come first?
私の用事が先でしょ
Right.
ああ
そういえば ふたりで待ち合わせしてたんだよな？
Yeah... You two were waiting
here together, weren't you?
やきもちやいてくれた？
Were you jealous?
Thanks, Lulu.
ありがとう ルル
Can't you wait? First we should...
待ってくれないかな 先に
さあ いきましょう スザクくん
Come on, let's go, Suzaku!
Wait! Hold it!
ああ　ちょっちょっと
ここは戦場になる
This place is about
to become a battlefield.
シャーリーの安全を考えれば
And I can't think of any place safer
for Shirley to be than with Suzaku!
スザクと一緒にいるのが一番いいはず
ジェレミア ゴットバルトか
Jeremiah Gottwald?
I am.
そうだが
何？防弾対策を
What?!
He's bulletproof!
I see. Lelouch has
used his Geass on you.
なるほどルルーシュのギアスにかかっているのか
え？あれ？
Wha?
It's not just that Geass doesn't work on him.
He has the power to cancel it as well.
ギアスがきかないだけではない
解除する力もあるのか
火事だ！テロだ！
Fire?!
Terrorists?!
That's it, come up
and get me, Orange!
さあ あがってこいオレンジ
なんだい？大事な話って
So, what was so important
to talk to me about?
私は 私はルルが好き
I... I love Lulu.
スザク君は嫌い？
Do you hate him, Suzaku?
僕は  好きだった
I...
I liked him... once.
今は？
And now?
変だと思ったんだ
I thought something was wrong.
前はあんなに仲がよかったのに
You used to be so close.
Did you have a fight?
ケンカでもしたの？
許せないんだ
I can't forgive him.
許せないことなんてないよ
Nothing is unforgivable.
それはきっとスザク君が許さないだけ
All that means is you're
not willing to forgive him.
You don't want to forgive him.
許したくないの
I forgave him a long time ago.
私はもう とっくに許したわ
シャーリー 君は
Shirley... What are you...
消防に連絡は？
Did you call the fire department?
The army comes first, doesn't it?
In a case like this...
軍のほうが先じゃないのか？このケースは
ナイトオブセブンの枢木スザクだ
Knight of Seven, Suzaku Kururugi!
あ これは
M- My Lord!
テロの可能性がある
This may be a terrorist act.
これより周辺の警察および消防は 自分が監督する
From here on, I'll take command of the
perimeter policing and fire fighting.
イエス　マイロード
Yes, My Lord!
I'd also like you
to protect that girl there.
それと君には 彼女を保護してほしい
なんだ？会議中だぞ
What is it?
We're in the middle of a meeting.
知るかよ俺がよばれてない会議なんかよ
Like I care?
Ain't no meeting I was invited to!
ゼロから緊急通信だ
We got an emergency call from Zero.
Something weird's going on over there.
なんか様子がおかしい
ゼロ 扇だ
Zero! It's Ohgi.
What's happened? What's the emergency?
If it's about the guys from Taiwan, right now we're...
何かあったのか？緊急って
台湾の人たちなら今
Ohgi!
扇
That voice!
その声は！
Hang on, big brother!
まってて 兄さん
一般人の避難誘導 完了しました
Evacuation of the bystanders has been completed.
ルル
Lulu...
車の中にどうぞ
Please get into the car.
It's the Knight of Seven's orders.
ナイトオブセブン様のご命令ですから
Wha?! Miss, come back!
あ 待ちなさい!君！
まっててルル
Hang on, Lulu! I won't leave you alone!
ひとりっきりになんて　させないから
You won't escape me.
逃がしはしない
どこなの？ルル
Where are you, Lulu?
やっぱり 戦ってるんだ
He must be fighting.
ルルは 一人で
Lulu's fighting... All alone.
A mechanical body...
A Geass Canceler...
機械の体 ギアスキャンセラー
執念は一流だなオレンジ君
Your vengefulness is certainly
top-class, my dear Orange!
This isn't vengeance. It's loyalty!
執念ではないこれは忠義
I hate hearing talk like that.
気にいらないな
あの皇帝のどこに 忠節をつくす価値がある？
What value does that emperor
have to earn such loyalty?!
What... have... you?!
う な に
From your performance,
I figured you must use sakuradite.
その性能 やはりサクラダイトをつかっていたか
A Gefjun Disturber!
ゲフィオン ディスターバー
Well, well,
you've done your homework.
ほうよく勉強しているじゃないか
Then you must know that when this
sakuradite disruption system is complete,
ならわかるだろう？
サクラダイトに干渉するこのシステムが完成すれば
環状線内の都市機能をすべて麻痺させられる
we can paralyze every city
function within the train's loop line.
つまり トウキョウが静止する
In other words,
bring Tokyo to a halt.
ありがとう
Thank you.
You've made an excellent test case.
君はいいテストケースとなった
ロロ
Rolo!
Shirley...
シャーリーさん
こたえて ロロ
Answer me, Rolo.
あなたは ルルが好き？
Do you... Do you love Lulu?
さあ話してもらおうか
Now then, will you tell me?
Where is the Order located?
Where is V.V.?
嚮団の位置をV.V.の居場所を
You're the one... who will talk here!
話すのは そちらのほうだ
What?!
何？
I have... my reasons...
私には 理由がある
忠義を貫く覚悟が
to hold onto my loyalty!
確かめなければならぬ真実が
I must know the truth for certain!
バカな！動けるはずがない！
Impossible! He shouldn't be able to move!
Lelouch...
Why did you adopt the role of Zero?
ルルーシュよ
おまえはなぜゼロを演じる？
Why turn against your homeland of Britannia?
And become an enemy of your own father?!
祖国ブリタニアを 実の父親を敵にまわす？
俺が ルルーシュ ヴィ ブリタニアだからだ
Because I am Lelouch vi Britannia!
はっ
俺の父ブリタニア皇帝は 母さんを見殺しにした
My father, the Britannian emperor,
let my mother die!
And in doing so,
stole Nunnally's sight, her legs!
そのためにナナリーは　目と足を奪われ
He stole our futures from us!
俺たちの未来まで
知っています
I know.
私もあそこにおりましたから
Because I was there, too.
With my mother?!
母さんの？！
It was my first assignment.
初任務でした
敬愛するマリアンヌ皇妃の護衛
Guarding Lady Marianne,
whom I loved and respected!
しかし 私は守れなかった
But I couldn't protect her!
I couldn't carry through
the loyalty I had for her!
忠義を果たせなかったのです
それで純血派を
And so you founded the Purebloods?
Master Lelouch... You became Zero
for Lady Marianne's sake, didn't you?
ルルーシュ様
あなたがゼロとなったのはやはりマリアンヌ様のためであったのですね
おまえは 俺を殺しに来たのではなく
You didn't come here
to kill me, did you?
私の主君は V.V.ではなく
The one I follow is not V.V.
It's Lady Marianne...
マリアンヌ様
これで思い残すことは ない
Now I can die without any regrets...
ジェレミア卿！
Lord Jeremiah!
うあっ 殿下
My prince!
ジェレミア ゴットバルトよ
Jeremiah Gottwald,
your loyalty is still needed.
貴公の忠節はまだ終わっていないはず
そうだな？
Isn't that right?
イエス　ユア　マジェスティ
Yes, Your Majesty!
私は ルルが好きあなたはどう？
I love Lulu.
What about you?
好きだよたったひとりの兄さんだもの
I love him. He's my only brother.
あなたは 味方なのねルルの
Then you're on Lulu's side, aren't you?
私も仲間に入れて！私もルルを守りたいの！
Please, let me join you!
I want to protect Lulu, too!
取り戻してあげたいの！ルルの幸せを！
I want to bring back
Lulu's happiness!
妹のナナちゃんだって いっしょに
So he can be back together
with Nunna, his sister!
ああ ジェレミアを先行させた
Right, I've sent Jeremiah on ahead.
障害があれば 彼が排除する
He'll take care of
any obstacles there are.
戦うなよ もう味方だからな
Don't fight him!
He's on our side now!
シャーリー！
Shirley!
誰がこんな
Who did this?!
Lulu? I'm glad...
We can talk at the very end...
ルル？よかった最後に　話せて
This isn't the end!
I'll call a doctor! So, just!
最後じゃない 今医者を呼ぶだから
I've been so afraid...
since I got my memories back...
私ね 記憶が戻ってすごくこわかった
A fake teacher...
偽物の先生 記憶のない友達
Friends without memories...
みんなが　嘘を　ついてる
Everyone was just... lying...
世界中が私を見張ってるような　気がして
I felt like the entire world was
watching my every move.
That's the world you've been
fighting against, all alone, isn't it?
ルルは　こんな世界で 一人で戦ってたんだね
All alone...
たった一人で
That's why... Why I wanted to be the
one person who'd be honest to you.
だから私は 私だけは
ルルの本当になってあげたいって
シャーリー
Shirley...
I love you, Lulu.
私 ルルが好き
お父さんを巻き込んだってわかってても
Even knowing how you got my father
caught in all this, I still couldn't hate you...
嫌いには　なれなかった
Even though you made me
forget everything...
ルルが全部忘れさせてくれたのに
それでも　また　ルルを好きになった
Even after that,
I fell in love with you again.
記憶をいじられても
Even though my memories were tampered with,
I fell in love with you again.
また好きになった
ダメだ！死ぬな！シャーリー！
No! Don't die! Shirley!
何度　生まれ変わっても
No matter how many times I'm reborn,
I'll keep falling in love with you, Lulu...
きっとまた ルルを好きになる
これって運命なんだよね
I guess this is just fate.
Don't die, Shirley!
Don't die! DON'T DIE!
死ぬな！シャーリー！死ぬな！
死ぬな！
So, it's all right, Lulu...
だから いいよね　ルル
Even if I'm reborn,
I'll fall in love with you.
生まれ変わっても また
ルルを好きになっても
何度も　何度も　好きに　なる から
Over and over...
I'll keep falling in love with...
シャーリー
Shirley... Shirley!
シャーリー!
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
かつてＣ.Ｃ.は俺に言ったギアスは王のちからだと
C.C. once told me something.
That Geass was the power of kings.
おまえを孤独にすると
ならば　これは
シャーリー俺はどうやって償えばいい
That it would isolate me.
Then this must be what she meant.
教えてくれ　教えて
Shirley...
I wanted to apologize to you.
I had to apologize to you!
For having involved you with Geass too much.
For making you the sacrifice.
How do I make up for this?
Tell me, please. Tell me!
GEASS HUNT